Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone|2001
Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets|2002
Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban|2004
Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire|2005
Harry Potter und ein Stein|2006
Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix|2007
Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince|2009
Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 1|2010
Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 2|2011
Harry Potter and the Untold Stories of Hogwarts|2012
Harry Potter and the Cursed Child|2016
Harry Potter: A History of Magic|2017
